thecatsite.com 2002-06-04

# TheCatSite.com - Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement 

At The Cat Site (TCS) we care about your privacy concerns. Please read the following statement to learn about our privacy policy.

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. TCS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. This includes links to our associates - Amazon, Pets.com, PetsMart, Gifts.com and AmericanGreetings.com.

**Cookies**

We try to refrain from unnecessary use of cookies on TCS. However, cookies are used for two purposes -

  * The TCS weekly poll, where the cookie is used solely to check whether or not a visitor has already voted for the poll. Visitors that have voted are presented with the poll results automatically (rather then being presented with the voting button again). The poll cookie expires by itself within one day. 
  * The TCS forums, where cookies are used to store your unique user id number and your password if you are a registered member. If you have chosen in your profile, this will automatically fill in your username and password in any place where you need them. It is recommend that you use these forums with a cookie-enabled browser. If you do not, you will have to type in your username and password every time you want to post.

**Forms**

Our site uses a feedback form for visitors to send us their impressions, ideas and criticism of this site. In this form, we collect visitor's contact information (name and email address). This information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. A visitor's e-mail address is not shared with or sold to any third parties. If you do not want us to know any of the information above, please do not submit the feedback form. 

**Newsletter**

Our site also allows you to sign up for a free newsletter. At this time, the list is served through Topica. Your e-mail address is not shared with or sold to any third parties. Only our staff and Topica's have access to the e-mail addresses. You can unsubscribe from the newsletter at sending a blank email to:  
[TheCatSite-unsubscribe@topica.com](mailto:TheCatSite-unsubscribe@topica.com). 

**Polls**

Our occasional online polls ask visitors for information regarding their cats. Note that no demographic or profile data is collected by the polls. We use this data learn more about the cat lovers who visit TheCatSite and as an added feature of educational and entertainment purposes. This information may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We do not share a visitor's individual information. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Aggregate data collection for Statistical analysis**

We currently use HitBox.com as a data collection service. HitBox.com ensures us that it collects only aggregate data. We receive only statistical data regarding broad characteristics of our visitors as a group. We have no access to any personal information about any of our visitors.

Please review HitBox.com's Privacy Statement for more information. [http://www.websidestory.com/privacy](http://www.websidestory.com/privacy/)

**Legal Disclosures of Information**

Except under the following circumstances, TCS will not share your personally identifiable information with a third party without your prior consent. There are a limited number of situations where we may disclose your personal information to others without first receiving your consent: (1) when legally ordered to do so by a lawful subpoena or court order, (2) if we believe conduct by you will harm the property or rights of TCS , or (3) under exigent circumstances to protect the physical safety of TCS, its employees, users or the general public.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact  

This statement was generated with help from [PageResource.com](http://www.pageresource.com/).

Back to Top
